export const data = [
  {
    question:
      "This is defined as a group of cells with a similar structure and function.",
    option1: "Tissue",
    option2: "Organ",
    option3: "Organism",
    option4: "Molecules",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which cavity is the brain located?",
    option1: "Neural cavity",
    option2: "Abdominal cavity",
    option3: "Vertebral cavity",
    option4: "Cranial cavity",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "A transverse plane will cut a body or organ into:",
    option1: "Anterior and Posterior",
    option2: "At an angle",
    option3: "Left and Right",
    option4: "Superior and Inferior",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The sternum is (     ) to the heart.",
    option1: "Posterior",
    option2: "Anterior",
    option3: "Inferior",
    option4: "Right",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many bones are found in the adult human skeleton?",
    option1: "200",
    option2: "206",
    option3: "250",
    option4: "232",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you had to get orthopedic surgery to mend your torn meniscus, what largest joint in the body would you have to get repaired?",
    option1: "Elbow",
    option2: "Knee",
    option3: "Ankle",
    option4: "Shoulder",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Of the three principal layers that make up human skin, what name is given to the outer most layer that provides a waterproof and protective barrier?",
    option1: "Dermis",
    option2: "Endodermis",
    option3: "Epidermis",
    option4: "Hypodermis",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The islets of Langerhans are groups of cells that produce insulin and glucagon located in what organ of the body?",
    option1: "Kidney",
    option2: "Liver",
    option3: "Pancreas",
    option4: "Spleen",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The chloecyst is another name for what small organ that stores bile?",
    option1: "Spleen",
    option2: "Gallbladder",
    option3: "Pancreas",
    option4: "Appendix",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Starting at the lower back and running down both legs, which nerve is the longest and widest in the human body?",
    option1: "Sciatic nerve",
    option2: "Ulnar nerve",
    option3: "Saphenous nerve",
    option4: "Femoral nerve",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Components of the central nervous system include all of the following except the:",
    option1: "Spinal nerves",
    option2: "Diencephalon",
    option3: "Spinal cord",
    option4: "Cerebellum",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The term “rostral” means:",
    option1: "Towards the dorsal aspect",
    option2: "Towards the nose",
    option3: "Towards the ventral aspect",
    option4: "Towards the tail",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which sulcus separates the pons from the midbrain?",
    option1: "Inferior Pontine Sulcus",
    option2: "Ventral Sulcus",
    option3: "Lateral Sulcus",
    option4: "Superior Pontine Sulcus",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The trigeminal nerve arises from the brain at the level of the:",
    option1: "Medulla",
    option2: "Midbrian",
    option3: "Mid-Pons",
    option4: "Diencephalon",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In early embryogenesis, the notochord develops in the midline from the:",
    option1: "Floor plate",
    option2: "Mesoderm",
    option3: "Ectoderm",
    option4: "Neural Plate",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The secondary embryonic brain vesicle that gives rise to the pons and cerebellum is the:",
    option1: "Mesencephalon",
    option2: "Telencephalon",
    option3: "Myelencephalon",
    option4: "Metencephalon",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The following is NOT true about retinal cones:",
    option1: "They produce sharp images, when excited",
    option2: "They are used in bright light",
    option3: "They need retinol to work ",
    option4: "They are less numerous than the rods",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ossicle that gets moved by the vibrations of the tympanic membrane is: ",
    option1: "Malleus",
    option2: "Incus",
    option3: "Stapes",
    option4: "Anvil",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The function of arrector pili muscle is:",
    option1: "To contract to squeeze oil from the sebaceous glands",
    option2: "To squeeze the sweat out of glands",
    option3: "To contract in order to produce heat for heat regulation",
    option4: "To raise the hairs in upright position",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "he following brain waves are produced during the REM period of sleep cycle:",
    option1: "Beta waves",
    option2: "Alpha waves",
    option3: "Keppa waves",
    option4: "Delta waves",
    ans: 1,
  },
];
